<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Meetings on Masquers - Official Website</title><link>https://masque.rs/meeting/</link><description>Recent content in Meetings on Masquers - Official Website</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://masque.rs/meeting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Minutes - March 4, 2022</title><link>https://masque.rs/meeting/march-4-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://masque.rs/meeting/march-4-2022/</guid><description>Attendance Sponsors Anna Seat Aaron Smith Officers Aaron &amp;ldquo;Radar&amp;rdquo; Bishop - President Matthew Jordan - Vice President Kaeli &amp;ldquo;Sushi&amp;rdquo; Maxwell - Treasurer Goldie Snow - Secretary Kayla Ford - Grievance Officer Sadie Stone-McCarty - Historian Attendees Karley Jones Ethan King Danica Rowe Ariana Snell Call To Order Time: 12:35 PM
Approval of Previous Minutes Previous minutes for both the special meeting and the previous meeting were discussed.</description></item><item><title>Special Minutes - February 18, 2022</title><link>https://masque.rs/meeting/february-18-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://masque.rs/meeting/february-18-2022/</guid><description>Preface This is a special meeting to vote in the vacant positions in the club.
Attendance Sponsors Anna Seat Aaron Smith Officers Aaron &amp;ldquo;Radar&amp;rdquo; Bishop - President Matthew Jordan - Vice President Kaeli &amp;ldquo;Sushi&amp;rdquo; Maxwell - Treasurer Goldie Snow - Historian Attendees Kayla Ford Karley Jones Ethan King Danica Rowe Ariana Snell Sadie Stone-McCarty Call To Order Time: 12:44PM
Approval of Previous Minutes N/A</description></item><item><title>Minutes - February 11, 2022</title><link>https://masque.rs/meeting/february-11-2022/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://masque.rs/meeting/february-11-2022/</guid><description>Preface As no formal minutes were recorded, the following is a summation of notes as remembered by the author.
Attendance Sponsors Anna Seat Aaron Smith Officers Aaron &amp;ldquo;Radar&amp;rdquo; Bishop - President Matthew Jordan - Vice President Kaeli &amp;ldquo;Sushi&amp;rdquo; Maxwell - Treasurer Reason: Work Ryland Asher - Secretary Reason: No longer a member True Williams - Grievance Officer Reason: No longer a member Goldie Snow - Historian Attendees Kayla Ford Karley Jones Reason: Prior obligations Ethan King Danica Rowe Reason: Prior obligations Ariana Snell Sadie Stone-McCarty Call To Order Time: 12:39 PM</description></item></channel></rss>